digdang.com 2014-12-17

# Dig Dang Privacy Policy - Dig Dang!

**DIGDANG.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

 Protecting the privacy of all of our users is an ongoing commitment of DIGDANG.COM. This Privacy Policy, which applies to all websites and services provided under the DIGDANG.COM names and marks, explains how DIGDANG.COM treats personal information that we collect and receive. Personal information is information about you, not otherwise publicly available, that personally identifies you; personal information may include your name, location, e-mail address, birth date, or other identifying information. 

 DIGDANG.COM has established registration and sign-in procedures which, in conjunction with this Privacy Policy, help ensure the privacy of information provided to DIGDANG.COM by its visitors and members while using DIGDANG.COM websites. You should be aware that this Privacy Policy applies only to the DIGDANG.COM website and services, and not to any other websites you may visit before or after DIGDANG.COM. 

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND WHO IS COLLECTING IT**

When you register to become a Member of a DIGDANG.COM website, DIGDANG.COM collects certain information such as your first and last name, e-mail address, your country of location, and gender, as well as information about each Member's use of DIGDANG.COM features and contributions of content (collectively, "Membership Information"). In addition, we may collect survey responses or other information regarding our users' interests and preferences. 

 DIGDANG.COM will not distribute, sell or rent any of the personal information about you to other people or nonaffiliated companies except to enable the provision of services or products you have requested or when we have your permission to do so. 

Some contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that will appear on the DIGDANG.COM websites may also be sponsored by other companies. These companies may also seek to collect personal information from you. You can avoid providing your personal information to these companies and sponsors by not participating in these contests, sweepstakes or promotions. In any event, you are encouraged to make yourself familiar with the privacy policy specific to any such event prior to your agreement to participate. 

 Please remember that any personal information voluntarily disclosed by you through e-mail, in public-view personal profiles, public-view uploaded materials, chat rooms, message boards, or intra-site message systems, can be seen and possibly used by others. Displaying personal information in such public fashion via our website or services may have unintended privacy implications for you. We encourage you to always remain aware of this possibility. DIGDANG.COM encourages you to use common sense and be cautious about what information you may provide on-line, whether through our websites or elsewhere on the Internet. 

 You acknowledge, consent, and agree that DIGDANG.COM may access, preserve, use, and disclose your Membership Information, including content uploaded to or downloaded from DIGDANG.COM's websites and services, if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: 

(a) enforce the DIGDANG.COM Terms of Service;
(b) respond to claims that any uploaded materials violate the rights of third-parties; 
(c) respond to your customer service requests; 
(d) comply with legal process; and/or 
(e) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of DIGDANG.COM, its users, or the public. 

**HOW DO WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

 Our primary goal is to provide members with the most useful and enjoyable experience on the Internet. Our advertisers will never be privy to your Membership Information, unless you permit us to give it to them so that they can provide you with products or services. Your e-mail address may be used by us for communications related to the DIGDANG.COM services, including but not limited to sending notices about new features, products, or other information of interest to you. 

 The DIGDANG.COM website is constantly evolving and changing in content and in features. Member-use information helps guide such changes and the evolution of our websites. Our advertisers and affiliates may be provided general information or data regarding membership usage patterns or interests, so that they too can better serve your needs and preferences, but such disclosure will not include individually identifiable information. The collection of usage and interest information allows us to provide a constantly evolving and user-sensitive package of services, products, and features that satisfy member needs, wants and desires but always with the priority of protecting individual member privacy. 

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's computer tied to information about the user. We may use either session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once a user closes the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on a user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. By showing how and when you use the Web Site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not and help in targeting advertisements based on your interests. Cookies also allow us to store the personal preferences that you set during each visit to our site, which in turn allows us to speed up your future activities at our site. 

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Specifically, this site uses the services of a variety of advertisers, rep firms and networks, including but not limited to: ValueClick, DoubleClick, AdGoto, Google and/or other various independent advertisers and/or networks for serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages when you visit our Web site. More particularly, the third-party advertising technology that we and our advertising partners use on this Web site uses information derived from your visits to this site to target advertising within this site. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp. In addition, we use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize certain of our our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site and to deliver more relevant advertising. To "opt-out," of the use of such Web beacons used by ad providers utilizing Doubleclick/Boomerang, please click here. http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx. 

**LOG FILES** Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, and report aggregate information to our advertisers, our corporate affiliates or consultants, or with third parties that perform a particular service on our behalf. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information, nor do we compile session activity reports by IP address. 

**NOTICE REGARDING CHILDREN**

 We at DIGDANG.COM take the online safety of children very seriously. DIGDANG.COM website and services are directed to adults. We do not allow children under the age of 14 to obtain User Names, and we do not intentionally collect any personal information from children under 14. 

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

 DIGDANG.COM may periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our websites. In addition, the date at the top of the Policy will indicate when the Policy has most recently been revised; we encourage you to periodically revisit the Privacy Policy to ensure that you are familiar with the current version. You are responsible for reviewing any revisions to this Policy, and your continued use of the DIGDANG.COM websites and services after any change to the policy constitutes your acceptance of the Policy. 

**CONTACTING DIGDANG.COM**

 If you have a privacy concern regarding any DIGDANG.COM website or this Policy, and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of the websites, should write to us by email at digdangmaster [at] gmail [dot] com. Alternatively, we can be reached by telephone at Tel: 905-482-3372 or our postal mail address: 

Attention: Privacy Officer  
7368 Yonge Street - Suite 309  
Thornhill, Ontario  
L4J 8H9  
Canada
